[{"answer": "Thank you.  Did you finish the upper field", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Those swimming breaks cut into the day, don't they", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "The middle colonies", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Anything about the convention in that place", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You all know why I am here.  I am not an orator and I will not try to convince you of the worthiness of our cause.  I am a soldier and we are at war and with the declaration of independence we all expect from that place, it will soon be a formal state of war.  In preparation for that, eight of the thirteen colonies have levied money in support of a that place.  I ask that place to be the ninth", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "that place and that place are not as far from that place as you might think and the war they're fighting is not for independence of one or two colonies.  It's for the independence of a nation", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Father, I've lost respect for you. I thought you were a man of principle", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "When I have children, I hope I don't hide behind them", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "How did this... how did I let this happen", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I should have known... once I would have... I used to be wary... and today I watched my son killed before my eyes... your sister civilized me and I damn myself for having let her..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I should have known... once I would have... I used to be wary... and today I watched my son killed before my eyes... your sister civilized me and I damn myself for having let her..", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I've done nothing and for that I am ashamed", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Green Dragoons came to my home, killed my son, my friend.  It was that place himself", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I'm sorry I wasn't here for this", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Not me, you.  I'm going north with every that place regular I can find to reinforce that place or he won't last six weeks", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Not held, just slowed down", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Not held, just slowed down", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "They'd be better off, but the cause wouldn't be", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "If you're here only for revenge, you're doing a disservice to him as well as yourself", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You know how old I am", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yes, quite, but you should know that..", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Yes... you will wait", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Apology accepted", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Colonel will do", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Shall we proceed", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I'm familiar with how a formal negotiation is handled", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "That one is a bit more difficult", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "And what are inappropriate levels of hostile attention", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why didn't he come", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "He left us", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "There are some letters here from him.  Some are just to you", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You don't hate him", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I know that", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Of course, I do", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Everyone knows.  It's what made me a hero.  Me, my friend, all of us.  I got a medal.  Men bought me drinks. They still do sometimes.  Everyone knows what happened", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "And what do they know", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Colonel, let us help his soul find it's place with the Almighty and..", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Yes, he does", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Remember my friend", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Worse", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "That bad", "docId": "Patriot_1998.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Proud, priggish and competent.  A very bad combination in an adversary", "qsentId": 42}]